Daniel J. Lee

3004 Suncrest Drive, San Diego, CA 92116

<u>Dan.lee619@gmail.com</u>

<u>http://DanLee619.github.io</u>

<u>https://www.linkedin.com/in/daniellee619</u>

(619) 415-6367

Summary

Cisco Networking Academy graduate with outstanding written and verbal communication skills. Competent in a wide variety of programming languages. Experienced in cabling, troubleshooting, and setting up networks. An avid learner excited to join a team where I can expand my technical knowledge and solve new problems.

Technical Skills

Routing & Switching: OSPF, EIGRP, RIP, BGP, RSTP, PVST+, ACLs, PAGP/LACP, PPPoE, GRE, IPsec, HSRP, Port-security Configurations, Spanning tree, VPNs, DHCP, DNS **Programming:** Java, JavaScript, PHP, MySQL, htmlHTML5, CSS3

Education

Cisco Networking Academy

2016

Cisco Certified Network Associate (CCNA)

San Diego Community Colleges (Mesa and Southwestern)

2013-2015

Completed 49 Units in Computer Science and IT

University of California Santa Barbara

2011

BA in Film and Media Studies; 3.7 GPA

Experience

The Party Staff Inc. 2014 - Present

Team Lead

- Act as liaison between clients and home office.
- Manage Party Staff employees to ensure that all work is done to client's satisfaction.
- Create event reports and perform other event related data-entry functions.

Comedy Juice 2014 - 2016

Marketing and Promotions Assistant

- Manage online marketing and promote upcoming shows via social media.
- Coordinate promotions and partnerships with local businesses.
- Operate the lights and soundboard for shows.